http://www.eurobond.co.uk/contact-us/privacy-policy/

HomeContact UsPrivacy policy
Site Service EngineersPrivacy policy
Privacy policy
This Privacy Policy indicates Eurobond Laminates Ltd procedures
regarding the collection and use of your personal information in
relation to the website (www.eurobond.co.uk), email marketing
activities and sms marketing activities. If you have any requests
or queries concerning your personal information, or would like to
be removed from our mailing list then please click here to contact
us, or alternatively, write to: Eurobond Laminates Ltd, Wentloog
Corporate Park, Cardiff, CF3 2ER.
This Privacy Policy will inform you in respect of the
following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you
on the website;
How this information will be used;
With whom the information may be shared; and
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and
distribution of the information.
1. What personal information do we collect?
We will collect the information entered into the contact us form
when you complete our contact us form. We will also collect your
email address when you subscribe to our e-newsletter.
Our system may also automatically record the following
information on your visit to our website:
your browser type (e.g. Netscape Navigator, Internet
Explorer)
your operating system (e.g. Microsoft Windows, Macintosh)
your IP address (a unique identifier for each connection to the
internet)
your domain name (e.g. yahoo.com, tiscali.co.uk)
This information is automatically collected and does not require
your input - the information is used to improve our facilities and
to provide you with an optimum website.
2. How this information will be used?
We respect your privacy and may use your information:
To log various usage and statistical information about your use
of our facilities to administer the website. Email addresses and
contact us information supplied will be used to send you product
information and company news from Eurobond Laminates Limited for
marketing purposes - providing you with details of new products and
services, to advise you of changes to our website; and to improve
our website, and to customise our website for you.
Our site provides an opt-in and opt-out facility so that you
only receive the e-newsletter if you choose to. At any time you can
opt-in or opt-out of receiving marketing information. If you choose
opt-in status, whenever we send you information, we will always
give you the opportunity to request your details to be removed from
our marketing list.
3. Who will we share your information with?
We may disclose your Information to:
Our regulators, lawyers and auditors persons where required by
law under a court order or subpoena third party service providers
or agents acting on our behalf.
(Our website may contain links to the websites of other
companies that are outside of our control. These websites are not
covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites through
our website then the operators of these sites may collect
information from you which will be used by them in accordance with
their own privacy policies, which may differ from ours.)
4. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use
and distribution of the information
Your information
Your Information will be retained by us for as long as the
purpose for which it was collected continues. It will then be
destroyed although copies may be retained if required to satisfy
our legal, regulatory or accounting requirements. By law, you are
entitled to a copy of the personal information we hold on you.
Opt-Out Procedure
You may choose not to receive any promotional communications
from us or our partners. We maintain an opt-out option on our
e-newsletters that you may choose to select at any time, if you do
not wish to receive such promotional communications from us or our
partners.
Changes / Modification
You may ask us to change or modify your information at any time.
Further if you are aware at any time that any of the information
that you have given to us has changed then please let us know at
the earliest opportunity of the changes that need to be made to
your information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If we change this policy, we will post the new policy on our
website. If the change means that we will use your information
differently, we will notify you. You may accept the change of use,
or if you do not, we will continue to use your information in
accordance with the policy under which it was collected.
Our Pledge to You
We pledge our intention to meet our obligations under this
Privacy Policy statement, and to comply with the requirements of
the Data Protection Act 1998.
About UsCompany policiesTechnical/site serviceSupply Chain PartnersInternational ProjectsEurobond CPDsCustomer CharterCareersLow RiskFire
PerformanceEnvironmental
PerformanceCase studiesSheffield UTCNational Graphene InstituteCUBRIC CardiffThe Old Dairy, South RuislipElliott's Field, RugbyThe Gateway BuildingMagna InternationalMcArdle SkeathBuilding solutionsExternal solutionsEuropanelRainspanRockspanRoofspanInternal solutionsFiremasterColorcoat by Tata SteelColorcoat PrismaColorcoat SpecificationColorcoat ServicesApprovals and CertificationsNewsArticlesEurobond and Euroclad are go!!!!!Eurobond NRG panels light the way for energy savingsRainspan offers even more design possibilitiesEurobond Laminates launches new and improved websiteEurobond achieves responsible sourcing standardEurobond launches BIM libraryEurobond Christmas Opening Hours 2015Eurobond at Big 5 ExhibitionRequest Eurobond Middle East CPD SeminarEurobond Panels Achieve DCD ApprovalEurobond achieve ISO14001The new face of retail - RainspanCreative solutions with RainspanEnvironmental excellenceEurobond become SCI assessedMulti Facade Building envelopesFiremaster Cost SavingCharity Cycle RideEurobond launches RoofspanEurobond strengthens Board with two new Director appointmentsThe Offsite Construction ShowChristmas Opening Hours 2015-16Big 5 Dubai 2015BMAP Expo 2015 Officially Opens its DoorsTechnical Feature: BIMEurobond named as finalist for Welsh Business AwardRaising Money for Whizz-KidzEurobond triumphs at Welsh Business AwardsEurobond Cycle Team Supports Local CharityOffsite Construction Show 2016Sheffield UTC - Europanel - Rainspan Case StudyNational Graphene Institute - Rainspan Case StudyCardiff Cubric - Case StudyThe Old Dairy, South RuislipElliott's Field, RugbyThe Gateway Building - Thames Valley Science ParkNew Generation Colorcoat Prisma From Tata SteelEurobond wall & ceiling solutions to be showcased at the Data Centre World exhibitionLatest case study featuring Eurobond Europanel specification in new 21,000 sq m factory, discoverNew case study available featuring Eurobond FiremasterDownloadsBrochuresAnnual Inspection FormExportBIMCE MarkingContact UsSite Service EngineersPrivacy policy
We use cookies on our website www.eurobond.co.uk. To find out more about the cookies we use, please visit our Cookie Policy & Control page.
Please click “Accept and close” to accept the use of cookies on our website.
If you do not click “Accept and close” but continue to use this website: you thereby consent to the use of all Eurobond’s cookies and third party cookies for the purposes of improving performance, improving functionality and audience measurement, in accordance with the terms laid out in our Cookie Policy & Control page; and we will assume that you have read and understood our Cookie Policy & Control page.
Accept and close
